《女子监狱》
第二季第十集
老天爷
Oh, my God.
很差劲对吗
Horrible, wasn't it?
最差劲了
The worst.
你这个做得真差劲
You're really bad at that.
让我服务你好吗
Can I do you?
你不必问
You don't have to ask.
我从来没有过真正地...
I've never really...
为女人口交过吗
Gone down on a woman before?
我是说
I mean...
没有
No.
你算是哪门子的女同啊
What kind of a lesbian are you?
摸咪咪的
The boob-touching kind.
那好吧
All right, well...
你准备好"俯身"一试吗
Are you ready to take the plunge...
可以这样说
so to speak?
你会教我吗
Are you gonna coach me through it?
当然
Yeah.
该死
Shit.
阿姆斯特丹现在几点
What time is it in Amsterdam?
我不知道
I have no idea.
等我一下
Okay, um, give me a second.
对不起  生意上的事
I'm sorry, it's business.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你要喝杯水吗
Do you want a glass of water?
这也是反应之一吗
Is that a part of it?
脱水
Hydration?
搞什么
What the...
艾丽克斯
Alex!
老天  你妈的搞什么
Jesus! What the fuck?
住手  西尔维
Stop, Sylvie!
-住手  西尔维  妈的  -婊子
- Stop it, Sylvie! Shit! - Bitch!
老天
Jesus.
她打我
She... she attacked me.
-你妈的开什么玩笑  -别这样  帕波
- Are you fucking kidding? - Stop. Piper...
她就这样闯了进来
She just broke in here.
我住在这里
I live here!
是的
She does.
这是我的女友  你这个婊子
That's my girlfriend, you whore.
不
No.
把她赶出去
Get her the fuck out of here.
我会的
Okay, I will. I'm gonna get
我会让她走  然后我们谈谈
her out of here and then we're gonna talk.
我说了  让她滚  立刻
I said, get her out! Now!
西尔维  别这样  西尔维
Sylvie. Come on, Sylvie.
你的女友
Your girlfriend?
很复杂  帕波
It's complicated, Piper.
真操蛋
This is so fucked up.
对不起  我应该说的
I'm sorry, I should've said something.
你以为呢
You think?
你受伤了吗  她打伤你了吗
Are you hurt? Did she hurt you?
她揍了我的脸
She punched me in the face.
对  很痛
Yes, it hurts.
妈的  我另一只鞋呢
Fuck, where is my other shoe?
我只是  不断见到你
I just... I kept seeing you around and...
我喜欢你  然后你打来电话
You know, I liked you, and then when you called...
闭嘴  别说了  你越描越黑
Okay, stop it. Please don't. You're making it worse.
给
Here.
你找到另一只鞋子了吗
Did you find your other shoe?
算了
Forget it.
你没鞋怎么走回家
What? You can't walk home without your shoes.
你的鞋子很漂亮
They're nice shoes.
马歇尔百货买的  操你妈
They're from Marshalls. Fuck you!
脱衣服
Strip.
你也早上好
Good morning to you, too.
你喷了香水吗
You wearing perfume?
的确是的
I am, in fact.
我离开家前喷了点身体喷雾
I put on a little spritz right before I left the house.
你鼻子很灵
You have a good nose.
我有时会在耳后擦杏仁精
I put almond extract behind my ears sometimes.
让我闻起来一股曲奇味
Makes me smell like a cookie.
别废话了  下蹲咳嗽
Anyway, let's get to the squat and cough.
好的
Okay.
瞧瞧  她来啦
Well, well, there she is.
-浪子回来了  -是的
- The prodigal daughter returns. - Yep.
还没到早上8点
It's not even 8:00 A.M.
我已经被揩了三次油了
And I've already been felt up three times.
-怎么样  -摸奶头摸得不够
- How was it? - Not enough nipple play.
好笑
Funny.
这么说你不想谈
So you don't wanna talk about it?
我还在慢慢接受中
I'm, uh, still processing, you know.
和老年人尴尬的交谈
Awkward conversations with old people,
糟糕的干酪盘  葬礼
bad cheese plates, a funeral,
婚礼  麦芽啤酒
a wedding, malt liquor.
48小时体验一辈子
A whole lifetime in 48 hours.
你知道什么感觉很奇怪吗
You know what was so weird?
用非塑料的盘子吃东西
Eating off of plates that weren't plastic.
感觉好重
They felt so heavy.
你有空闲时间吗
Did you by any chance have time?
我有
I did.
我有些不敢问
I'm afraid to ask.
很棒  非常棒
It was great. It was really great.
真是皇后区的一处好地方
And that is such a cute part of Queens.
我之前没怎么去过
I've never spent much time there.
你进去了吗
Did you go in?
时间不长
For a minute.
生意很好  还排了队
You know, it's doing really well. There was even a line.
你点了什么吗
But you ordered something?
点了  我...
Yes! I, um...
点了那种甜甜的
One of those... the sweet...
-乳酪面包吗  -是的
- Vatrushki? - Yes.
-乳酪面包  -是的
我会在夏天用蜜桃泥做
I do them with peach puree in the summertime.
太好吃了
Delicious.
那地方真漂亮  红妈
It's such a beautiful place, Red.
我明白你为什么为之如此骄傲
I can really see why you are so proud of it.
真的谢谢你
Thank you. Really.
我的儿子们告诉我生意很差
My boys had told me business was bad, and, you know,
在这里  我无能为力
from in here, there's nothing I can do.
感谢上帝有了转机
Thank God they turned it around.
你和莱瑞怎么样了
So, how was it with Larry?
奇怪  伤心  正式分手
Bizarre, sad, officially over,
他上了别人
and he fucked someone else.
他告诉你的吗
He told you this?
在醉酒极度悲伤的性交过程中说的
In the middle of a drunken, grief-stricken sexual encounter.
你知道最奇怪的是什么吗
But you know what the weirdest thing was?
我甚至一点也不生气
I wasn't even mad. At all.
这也说得通  一报还一报
It kind of made sense. Tit for tat.
我们的情况是奶子换奶子
Or, well, tit for tit, as the case may be.
亲爱的
Oh, honey,
你心胸比我宽广
you're a bigger woman than I am.
-他上的谁  -我不想知道
- Who was it? - I didn't wanna know.
-少废话  -真的  我不想知道
- Oh, bullshit. - No, really, I didn't wanna know.
他告诉我  是我认识的人
He told me it was someone I know,
知道是谁只会更糟
and a name would just make it worse.
你知道谁最有可能吗  我们的邻居娜塔利
But you know who it probably was? Our neighbor, Natalie.
她是瑜伽教练
She's a Bikram teacher.
很嗲那种
She's very touchy-feely,
总是让我们去免费上课
she's always offering us lots of free classes.
但谁在乎啊  根本不重要
But who cares? It doesn't matter anyway.
我们分手了
We broke up.
是我先出轨的  不是吗
I'm the one who cheated first, right?
你有信
Some mail came for you.
是沃斯寄来的
It's from Vause.
感谢你为我抽出时间
And thank you for taking the time for me.
回头有漂亮的唇彩给你
You will be getting some very nice lip gloss.
别忘了  女士们
Don't forget, ladies,
正常饮食是1500卡路里
your usual meal is 1,500 calories.
不要暴食
Be aware of overeating.
有两份华夫饼
There's two waffles on there.
你妈的在做什么
怎么啦  她们多给烟我抽
谢谢
Thank you.
有话要对我说吗
You got something to say to me?
我的姑娘们需要你的座位
My girls need your seat.
我吃完后  她们就可以坐了
And when I'm done, they can have it.
吃完了吗
Done yet?
你真是一个无礼的女人
You are a very rude woman.
人家伤心死了
Oh, you wound me.
妈的  维  咱在这里疟了
Yo, damn, Vee! Yo, we like ballers up in here!
我不是说了吗  你能给别人所需时...
Didn't I tell y'all? When you got something people want...
今天早上
Yo, this morning,
爆牙克莱门蒂诺居然在浴室等我
Underbite Clementino was waiting for me in the bathroom
给我来个背部按摩
to give me a back massage.
-什么  -背部按摩
- What? - A back massage!
感觉我像是圣特鲁佩斯一艘游艇上的碧昂斯
Like I'm fucking Beyonce in a yacht in Saint-Tropez, okay!
下雨吧  贱人们
Make it rain, bitches.
小卖部女王驾到
Commissary queen in the hizzy!
妈的  感觉真好
Fuck, this feels good.
我把常那里扫荡了
I cleaned Chang out.
你什么都买走了
"You take-a the everything!
没有东西给其他女士了
Nothing reft for the other ladies."
我不是说过吗  维会照顾我们的
Yo, didn't I tell you that Vee was gonna take care of us?
制度关着我们  你就得找到应对的办法
System work you, you got to find a way to work the system.
-阿门  -赞美主啊  哈利路亚
- Amen! - Gloria, hallelujah!
谁给你剪的头发  丹妮塔吗
Who cuts your hair? Danita?
当然不是
Hell, no!
我才不会让那个屠夫拿着剪刀接近我
I wouldn't let that butcher near me with a pair of scissors.
我自己打理的
I do it myself.
别看后面  一团糟
Don't look at the back, it's a mess.
什么大场合
What's the occasion?
我儿子来看我
My son's coming to visit.
如果他没注意到  你别生气
Well, don't be upset if he doesn't notice.
男孩子蠢死了  他们永远不会注意到这种事
Boys are stupid. They never notice things like that.
迈克尔很久没见过我了
Michael hasn't seen me in a long time.
他从未来过
He's never come before.
为什么不来
Why not?
他很生气
He was pissed off.
或觉得丢人  或两者都有
Or ashamed. Or both.
是他举报我的
He turned me in.
那你打算在探视
So, you're strangling him
开始还是结束时掐死他
at the beginning of the visit or at the end?
他只有12岁  非常愤怒
He was only 12 and angry.
他经历了太多
He's been through a lot.
我会坐好  让他发泄  把怨气全发泄出来
I'm gonna sit back, let him vent. You know, get it all out.
要是我  就踢死他
Well, if it were me, I'd kick him to death,
但我们做父母的方式不同
but we all have our own way of parenting.
甘地这么做来抗议种姓制度
Gandhi did it to protest the caste system.
只有这样才能有所改变
It's the only way to make a real difference.
你就省省吧
You're wasting your breath.
你无法说服这些人绝食的
You're not gonna convince this crowd not to eat.
她是对的
She's right.
这碗麦片味道像大团鼻屎
I mean, this oatmeal tastes like a bowl of chunky boogers,
但妈的不吃还不舒服了
but fuck if it isn't comforting to keep shoveling it in.
这么说  你们都很满意现状
So I suppose you're all happy with the way things are going?
你们觉得这座监狱的现状非常好吗
You think the conditions in this prison are perfectly fine?
联邦政府的钱应该用在
That federal money should be
让女人在满是排泄物的隔间里洗澡
spent on making women shower in feces-soaked stalls
而她们反抗时却要遭受身体虐待吗
and face physical abuse if they resist?
来吧  简・方达[影星]  来点香肠
Come on, Jane Fonda, have a little bit of sausage.
对  就一小口  你看起来脸色苍白
Yeah, just a little bite. You look a bit pale.
已经多少天了
How many days has it been?
拜托  别烦她了
Come on, leave her alone.
修女
Sister?
我以为至少你会支持我
I thought you of all people would support me.
亲爱的  这里又不是关塔那摩监狱
Oh, honey, it's not Guantanamo.
就是
Yeah!
让一下  苏苏
Yeah, move over, Soso.
好吧  我一个人来
Fine. I'll do it alone.
你真是太无礼了
That is really disrespectful.
休假怎么样  给我带T恤了吗
How was furlough? Did you bring me back a T-shirt?
真他妈的  妹子
Holy shit, dude.
说什么
Well, what's it say?
慢着  让我猜猜
Wait, let me guess.
美女  抱歉我在芝加哥坑了你
"Hey, girl, uh, sorry I fucked you over in Chicago.
那是为你好  我给你舔阴户吧
It was for your own good. Let me lick your pussy."
可能吧  但我不知道
Probably, but I don't know.
-我还没看  -什么
- I haven't read it. - What?
老天  你意志真坚定啊
Man, that's some serious willpower right there.
你就不好奇吗
Aren't you curious?
我当然好奇  这是第一封我没扔掉的
Of course I'm curious. It's the first one I haven't thrown away.
那就看呗
So, fucking read it already.
-我来  -不用不用
- I'll do it. - No! No, no, no, no, no.
她就是想要这样
That is exactly what she wants.
对  当人们寄信
Yes, that is generally what
一般就是想让别人看
people want when they send a piece of correspondence.
她会说些什么我想听的话
What could she possibly say that I want to hear?
她是个说谎精
She's a liar.
从最开始  她就满口谎言
She's always been a liar. From the very beginning.
难道不是每个人都对每个人说谎吗
Doesn't everyone lie to everyone?
她知道如果她一直寄信
She knows that if she keeps sending these,
最终会打动我
eventually I will crack,
然后她会道歉
and then she'll apologize,
然后她会满口仁义  让她去死
and she'll say all the right things, and fuck that!
但你也不会把信扔掉
But you're not gonna throw it away either.
-你想她  -我当然想她
- You miss her. - Of course I miss her.
我讨厌她对我的影响力  我真是烦透了
I hate that she has this hold on me. I'm so sick of it.
麦片味道跟鼻屎一样
The oatmeal tastes like snot.
我要一杯  要一杯
I'll take a... shot. Shot!
没关系  我要这个
It's all good. Okay, I got this one.
太差劲了
Oh, that was terrible!
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我嘛
Oh, I just, um...
我听说了艳舞表演
I heard about the burlesque show.
-你呢  -我朋友瑞秋是演员之一
- You? - My friend Rachel's in it.
她和雷・罗曼诺的木偶一起表演
She does this routine with a Ray Romano puppet.
居然相当性感
It's surprisingly sexy.
那晚的事我很抱歉  帕波
Look, I'm really sorry about that night, Piper.
我不是那种做事遮遮掩掩的人
I'm not a shady person.
算了  没事的
Oh, come on, don't worry about it.
我以前没挨过揍
I mean, I've never been punched before.
这可能是很好的人生体验
It was probably a good life experience.
我说事情很复杂时是认真的
I meant it when I said that things were complicated.
恋爱关系对我来说是新尝试  我不知道
I'm new to this whole relationship thing. You know, I don't...
我不知道规则
I don't know the rules.
这就是问题所在对吗
That's the whole problem, isn't it?
守规矩一点也不好玩
Rules aren't any fun.
我不想打扰真爱
Listen, I don't want to stand in the way of true love.
如果那位是你未来的妻子
I mean, if that is your future wife out there,
请务必让我走开
by all means, tell me to back off.
但你追求我  我很喜欢
But you pursued me, and I liked it.
我
I've...
我从未感受过...
I've never felt...
我从未觉得自己是个
You know, I've never really thought of myself
性欲很强的人  但是
as a very sexual person, but...
自从...
ever since...
我想品尝你的味道
I want to taste what you taste like.
餐厅供应什么  红妈
What were they serving in there, Red?
内脏[屈辱]馅饼
Humble pie?
鸟肉[大麻]  生奶油[鞭打]老太太
Crow? Whipped old lady?
一直在练习双关冷笑话吗
Been practicing those?
自大汉堡  脸上的鸡蛋[耻辱]
High horse hamburger? Egg on your face?
你吃了你的帽子吗[说过的话错了]
Did you eat your hat?
-哥们  -嘿
- Hey, bud. - Hey.
还好不
How you doing?
你那次崩溃后  你那晚哭了没
Did you cry it out the other night after your little lady meltdown?
拜托  兄弟  放轻松
Oh, come on, man, relax. Shit, loosen up.
就像我妈经常说的  别一脸苦逼样
It's like my mom used to say, "Wipe that puss off your face."
直译为"把阴户从脸上拿开"
当然那是在我意识到  我喜欢脸贴着阴户前
'Course that was before I learned I liked puss on my face.
又是新的一天  本尼特
It's a new day, Benerino.
这他妈算什么  《狱中号角》
What the fuck is this? The Big House Bugle?
显然你支持这种犯人宣传活动
Clearly you supported this prisoner propaganda.
她们为我写了篇不错的封面故事
They did a nice cover story on me.
你们这些白痴
And none of you morons
没人看懂漫画里的那只海象是海利吗
caught on that the walrus in the comic is Healy?
我觉得很搞笑
I thought it was pretty funny.
你觉得这只穿高跟鞋
And who do you think is the pig in high heels
背着几包钱的猪是谁
carrying around the bags of money?
真难住我了
You got me there.
这垃圾是谁负责的
Who's in charge of this garbage?
应该是查普曼  犯人主编
That would be Chapman. Inmate-in-chief.
我不想再见到这种烂东西
I don't want to see this shit again.
也许你应该重新考虑下
You might want to reconsider.
你会需要全部的新闻宣传
You can use all the journalistic spin you can get.
为什么
Why?
你最喜欢的强奸犯警卫表现突出
Your favorite rapist guard has exceeded all expectations.
迪亚茨怀孕了
The Diaz girl is pregnant.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
今天早上做了检查
Tested her this morning.
上帝
Jesus.
坏坏的孩子他爸
Big, bad baby daddy,
你让他回来的
and you brought him back.
真他妈的  我得把握住局势
Fuck me. I gotta get out in front of this.
不能让门德斯知道这事  等我安排好再说
Mendez can't know anything until I frame the whole thing.
你让他继续工作吗
You're keeping him at work?
等我把事情安排好
Just until I get my ducks in a row.
这事得正确解决
This thing has to be handled right.
你要我为你保守这个秘密
You want me to keep this under wraps,
你就得为我做点事
you're gonna have to do something for me.
什么
What?
到时候
When it's time...
我来炒掉这个杂种
I get to fire the bastard.
好
Fine.
为什么是俄国人
So, why a Russian?
我不知道  我只是
I don't know. I just...
我做了些网上调查
I did some online research,
发现最受欢迎的邮购网站
and I found that the top-rated mail order sites
不是东欧就是东方的  所以
were either Eastern European or Oriental, so...
我觉得和俄国人少些文化障碍
I figured there'd be less cultural barriers with the Russians.
有金钱交易吗
And there was money exchanged?
对不起  我对这个不熟
I'm sorry, I'm not familiar with...
我不需要你对我品头论足
You know, I don't... I don't need your judgment, okay?
因为就所见而言
'Cause from the looks of it, you know,
我想你的爱情生活也不怎么样
I'm guessing your love life isn't so hot either.
也许你把你的经历投射到我身上  山姆
Perhaps you're projecting your experiences onto me, Sam.
少说些心理学废话
Let's cut the fucking psychobabble, okay?
我的老婆是我买来的  他妈的又怎样
I have a wife that I paid for. So fucking what?
我不需要你搬出这些教课书术语
I don't need you going around throwing out these textbook
就像那些有优越感的伪百事通一样
terms like some condescending know-it-all.
我也是靠这个吃饭的
This is what I do for a living, too.
我是个辅导员
I'm a counselor.
你为什么来这里
Why did you come here?
我他妈的也不知道为什么来这里
You know, I don't fucking know why I came here.
因为我他妈的不需要你的帮助
Because I don't need your fucking help.
因为我才是帮助他人的人
Because I'm the one that's helping people.
日复一日
All day long.
是吗
Do you?
你真的帮助了他人吗
Do you really help people?
他妈的当然了
You bet your ass I do.
老天  这些发辫痒死了
Man, these tracks itching something fierce.
我得把这些给维  让她能散出去给她的人
I gotta get these to Vee so she can get 'em out to her people.
寄邮票需要多少邮票
How many stamps do you need to send stamps?
你有时间吗
Yo, you got a second?
我知道你们在贩毒
I know y'all are dealing.
那又如何
Yeah, so?
你对我说谎  T
So, you lied to me, T.
说得你好像没卖过毒品一样
Like you never sold drugs.
我卖的是大麻  不是那些害人的
I sold weed. Not real shit.
害人到足够把你关在这里了
Real enough to get your ass locked in here.
别这么假清高
So don't be acting all high siddity.
怕你没注意到
In case you ain't noticed,
这里全是罪犯
this place is full of criminals.
我们也是其中两个
And we're two of 'em.
加那边的疯子有三个罪犯
Three, if you include cuckoo over here.
咱们有钱赚呐
Yo, we's getting paid, man.
咱们帮万岁  警察去死
Our crew rules. Fuck the police!
现在你们全成了黑帮分子吗
Oh, what, now you all gangster?
你们全他妈被洗脑了
Man, y'all are fucking brainwashed.
你嫉妒了
You're jealous.
嫉妒什么  你像个欺负人的小混混吗
Jealous of what? You acting like a hood rat corner kid?
你不知道我的出身
You don't know where I come from.
我没有老爸在军队  没父母管我
I ain't have no daddy in the army, parents looking out for me,
没有棉衣  你这个有钱人家的贱人
and a fucking winter coat, you bougie bitch.
别假装你了解我和我的人
So don't pretend like you know me or my people.
我以为你不想堕落到如此地步
I thought you wanted to be better than that.
滚出我的铺位
Get the fuck out of my bunk.
临时检查
Yo, it's a sweep.
他们临时检查
They sweeping.
快走  女士们
Let's go, ladies!
犯人们  立刻离开铺位
Inmates, outside your bunks, now!
全部不准动
Don't move a muscle.
让我看到你们吞什么藏什么
I see you swallow anything or tuck anything away,
就等着关禁闭吧
your ass goes to the box.
我想左边拔得太夸张了对吗
I think I did the left side too much. Right?
眉弯太高了吗
The arch is too high?
看起来
Eh, it kind of looks like
你这人疑神疑鬼的
you're really skeptical about everything.
我觉得狡猾的样子挺性感的
I think the leery look is hot, you know?
-A区宿舍  临时检查  -妈的
- A-Dorm! Sweep time! - Fuck!
他们会拿走我的唇膏
They're gonna take my lipstick.
临时检查  女士们
Sweep time, ladies!
妈的
Fuck!
真他妈的
Shit! Son of a...
犯人  出去
Inmate, outside!
非法食品  记一笔
Illegal foodstuffs. That's a shot.
指甲油  锋利镊子
Nail polish. Sharp tweezers.
你的通话时间没有了  犯人
There goes your phone time, inmate.
中大奖了
Jackpot!
恐怕这个可不是超强吸引性卫生棉条
I doubt these are super absorbent, huh?
这是谁的床铺  沃森
Whose bunk is this? Watson.
这些小卷卖多少钱
How much these little rollies going for, huh?
给自己找了点买卖吗
Got yourself a little business?
没有  长官
No, sir.
别跟我说什么没有
Don't you "No, sir" me!
快把你的黑屁股挪到禁闭室去
You start marching your pretty black ass to the SHU.
我知道你有多喜欢那里
I know how much you love it in there.
快走
Move!
给我
I'll take that.
你收到了我的卡
You have my card.
孩子们很可爱对吗
Kids are cute, right?
另一张准备买的卡是一只猫说"你喵完美"
It was between this or some cats that said, "You're purr-fect!"
是的
Yeah.
我的选择是正确的
I made the right choice.
你看起来不同了
You look so different.
不知怎的更温柔了  这是好事
Softer somehow. In a good way.
我让你留着这个
I'm gonna let you keep that.
没发现
Clear!
老天  瞧这一堆
Jesus, what a haul!
把这个撕开检查毒品后我就带它回家
I'm taking this home after I rip it open to check for drugs.
好可爱
It's adorable.
看这些东西
Look at all this stuff.
显然是有门路弄进来的
There are some serious open channels here.
你闻一下
Here, smell this, would ya?
好难闻
Whoa, that's awful.
闻一下
Smell it.
大便味
Oh, it smells like poo.
全闻起来是大便味
Yeah, it all smells like poo.
知道这意味着什么吗
You know what that means?
全是通过直肠弄进来的
It's all coming in through the rectal pipeline.
下蹲咳嗽检查太松懈了
Someone has been slacking with the squat and cough.
知道这意味着什么吗
You know what this means?
光看已经不够了  得开始捅了
It's not enough to look, we gotta start probing.
不能碰她们  这是违法的
We can't touch 'em. It's illegal.
我可不会把胳膊伸过去
I'm not sticking my arm up there.
那么伸手指呢  有什么不行
What about a finger? What's wrong with that?
偶尔伸根手指感觉不错啊
A finger's nice once in a while.
只能目测
Visual inspections only.
小小的指头  拜托
Tiny little finger? Come on.
我不知道你们  但我准备好做英雄了
I don't know about you all, but I'm ready to be the hero.
没什么能逃过我
Nothing's getting past me.
你看的和你想的不一样  就这样了
You didn't see what you thought you saw, end of story.
-那是什么  -老天  有完没完
- What was it, then? - Oh, Jesus, really?
我不会就此罢休的
Look, I'm not gonna leave you alone.
我什么也没做
I'm not doing anything.
你要和我一起去厕所吗
Do you wanna join me in the bathroom?
我要去那里  去拉屎
'Cause that's where I'm headed. To take a dump.
来吧  你可以把纸折整齐了给我
Come on, you can hand me neatly folded squares of paper
就好像你是宫廷侍从官  我是亨利八世
like you're the groom of the stole and I'm Henry VIII.
你给你今天的心理状态打几分
Well, how would you rate your state of mind today?
4吗
A four?
你有没有愤怒的想法  这种想法定期出现吗
You having any angry thoughts? They coming up regularly for you?
Are you having angry thoughts that are coming up regularly?
这是投射
That's projection.
什么意思
What does that mean?
你知道我是靠什么维生吗  我的工作是什么
You have any idea what I do for a living? What my job is?
我当然知道
Of course I do.
你为那些记过的女士们填写相关文件
You fill out the paperworks for the ladies that get shots.
我提供指导
I provide guidance.
我就人们的问题提出忠告
I counsel people with their problems.
我想创办一个支持小组
I'm thinking about starting a support group.
开展心理治疗
It's a therapy thing.
我觉得对这里的女性有帮助
I think the women here could really use it.
这里有些爱生气的贱人
There are some angry bitches around here.
但如果没有好处
But you know that ain't nobody gonna do nothing
是没人会理的
without getting something from it.
她们会有收获的
They will be getting something.
对她们的问题有帮助
Help with their problems.
不  我是说比如免费甜甜圈  不用干活
No, I'm talking about, like, free donuts, or days off work.
我印了些传单
I've, uh, printed out some flyers.
我想要你发出去
I'd like you to distribute them.
好的  海利先生
All right, Mr. Healy,
但我告诉你  没人会来的
but I'm telling you, no one's gonna come on their own.
你低估了她们
You're underestimating them.
这些女性经历了太多
These women have been through a lot.
她们会来的
They'll come.
没想到你们会对文学有兴趣
Didn't realize y'all had such literary interests.
我们希望你能给些建议
Yeah, well, we were hoping you could make a few suggestions.
因为我听说  你这个人很会提意见
'Cause from what I hear, you're quite the little critic.
-我有些想法  -是吗
- Yeah, I got some thoughts. - Yeah?
还有些问题
Yeah, and some questions.
你为什么让珍娜被关了禁闭
Like why you let my girl Janae get dragged off to seg.
她应该明白不能把违禁品放在铺位上
Well, she knew better than to keep contraband in her bunk.
现在她有许多独处的时间来考虑这个问题
Guess she got a lot of alone time now to think about it.
她不会有事的  只要她只想不出声
She'll be fine, so long as she thinks and doesn't speak.
你到底入不入伙
You in or out?
图书馆对我们来说是个好地方
The library is prime real estate for us.
你有地盘了  别在这里交易
Look, you got your spot. Deal out of there.
女囚们扎堆去仓库是说不通的
There's no reason for the inmates to flow through the warehouse.
连看看都是不对劲的
There's no excuse to browse.
而且  警卫已经嗅到了血腥味
Plus, the hacks got a taste of blood.
他们检查所有的工作地点只是时间问题
It's only a matter of time before they sweep all the work sites.
我不是小混混
I ain't no corner girl.
我喜欢这个地点
I like this spot.
所以你要么听话  要么要求调职
So you either get your ass in line or request a transfer.
我听说电工那边在招人
I hear Electrical is looking.
明白吗
You feel me?
我哪里也不去
I ain't going nowhere.
明白吗
You feel me?
迪亚茨女士  我们只是需要口头确认
Miss Diaz, we just need verbal confirmation
门德斯警官强暴了你  你能说出来吗
that Officer Mendez forced himself on you. Can you provide that?
你没看到吗
Didn't you see it?
这是为了文书工作
This is for our paperwork.
乔  如果你不在这里
Joe, I think Miss Diaz would be more comfortable
我想迪亚茨女士会自在些
if you weren't in the room.
有法律规定
Look, there are laws in place
犯人与监狱工作人员的性爱是非法的
which criminalize sex between prisoners and prison staff.
这意味着工作人员有性爱不当行为时
Which means that employees who engage in sexual misconduct
不能将对方同意作为辩护借口
cannot claim consent as a defense.
所以正式来说这是强奸
So, officially it's a rape,
没错  我们会这么说
yes, and we're all gonna call it that.
但我需要知道  女人对女人
But I need to know, girl-to-girl...
是你情我愿的吗
was it consensual?
我明白  你孤单  你想调调情
Listen, I get it. You're lonely, you want to flirt a little.
引起警卫的注意令你觉得很特别
Attention from a guard makes you feel special.
仅是那身制服就让人有性趣对吗
I mean, those uniforms alone can be a real turn-on, right?
就咱们之间说清楚
So, just between us,
我要知道你是否鼓励了他
I need to know if you encouraged him.
-是的  -我想也是
- Yes. - I thought as much.
你真给我惹了大麻烦  小姑娘
Well, you've created quite a headache for me, young lady.
现在我不仅要对你负责
And now not only am I responsible for you,
还要对你肚中的胎负责
but for your little spawn of the system.
所以帮个忙  亲爱的
So, do me a favor, sweetheart,
从现在开始  把你的双腿闭紧
from now on, keep your legs closed.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你正式毁了一个男人的生活
You've officially destroyed a man's life.
不  你得告诉她  如果银行周日关门
No, you gotta tell her that if the bank is closed on Sunday,
那么周一早上给她钱就他妈的没有滞纳金
that there's no fucking late fee if you pay her Monday morning.
-这种屁话不对  -我说了
- That shit's not right. - I did.
她依然要收你钱吗
And she's still trying to charge you?
是的
Mmm-hmm.
你要这样做
Okay, so here's what you gotta do.
你找根棒球棒
You get a baseball bat,
木头的  不要金属的
the wood kind, not the fucking metal kind,
一个大垃圾袋
and a big trash bag,
黑色的  不要看得透那种
the black kind, not the see-through kind...
迈克尔  你长大了
Michael, you look all grown up.
你一定长高了有4英寸
You must have grown, like, 4 inches.
现在叫迈克了
It's "Mike" now.
看看他的脚
Now, take a look at his feet.
我告诉他  他躺下去和站着一样高
I told him he's as tall lying down as he is standing up.
你想对我说什么
Anything you want to say to me...
都可以  明白吗
you can say it, okay?
也许我们应该玩游戏  好吗
Well, you know, maybe we should play a game. Hmm?
那边小孩用品里有扑克牌  怎么样
They got a deck of cards over there by the kids' stuff. Huh?
在探视室  可以拥抱两次
When in the Visitation Room, you're allowed two hugs,
到达和离开时分别一次
one on arrival and one on departure.
卫生间还没修好
Well, they still didn't fix the bathrooms,
湖边应该建挡土墙
and they were supposed to put in a retaining wall by the lake,
但现在只有几包沙袋
but there's just a couple of sandbags.
我查了FCP这个名字  并不存在
Well, I ran the name FCP and it doesn't exist.
查不到这家公司
No trace of the company.
你确定在卡车上看到的是这个名字吗
You sure that's the name you saw on the truck?
对  我肯定
Yeah, I'm positive.
我猜想
Well, my guess is that the
监狱给合同的公司
prison is giving inflated contracts to companies
要么是空壳公司  要么是菲茨核心的下属公司
that are either shells or subsidiaries of FitzCORE,
菲茨核心将回扣
and FitzCORE is paying
给杰森・菲格罗亚的竞选
kickbacks into the Jason Figueroa campaign.
我需要的是发票  我能看出谁在拿钱
What I need are invoices, so I can see who's getting paid.
是哦
Right.
不如这样
Well, what about...
不如拍些未完成品的照片
What about photos of all the unfinished work?
如果我能给你弄部相机
If I could get you a camera...
不  不如你给我弄部苹果手机
No, why don't you get me an iPhone
这样我能拍照  还能玩"糖果大爆险"
so then I can take pictures and play Candy Crush?
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
我之前跟你说过了
I told you before,
我不会以自由为代价  为你的署名文章冒险
I'm not risking my freedom for your fucking byline.
帕波  这个女人是罪犯
Piper, this woman is a criminal.
是吗  我也是
Yeah? Well, so am I.
要二吗
Collecting twos?
不要
Nope.
对我有用
Better for me.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
你把我打得落花流水
You're kicking my ass here.
对  到我发牌了
Yep. My turn to deal.
谢谢
Thank you.
南斯先生  你怎么来了
Mr. Nance, what brings you here?
菲格罗亚女士  你好吗
Miss Figueroa, how are you?
知道你来我监狱做什么我会更好
Better once I know what the fuck you're doing in my prison.
我来探视一位朋友
I was... visiting a friend.
那位朋友是谁
And what friend might that be?
我给你的办公室打过几个电话
You know, I've called your office a bunch of times.
是吗
Have you?
我五秒钟就能找出你在谁的探视名单上
I can find out whose list you're on in five seconds flat,
没必要玩游戏
so there's no need to play games here.
帕波・查普曼
Piper Chapman.
帕波・查普曼  你怎么认识她的
Piper Chapman. And how do you know Piper Chapman?
我们有共同的朋友
We have... mutual friends.
你看到这烂人了吗
You seeing this shit?
就好像他妈的看上我一样
I mean, it's like she's got a fucking hit out on me.
我想她要你的芝士泡芙
I think she wants some of those cheese puffs you got.
给她一点吧
Maybe just give her a few.
一定是这样  她看上我的泡芙了
Oh, yeah, that must be it. She's after my puffs.
莫里洛  你有探视者
Morello, you have a visitor.
到探视室报到  莫里洛
Report to Visitation, Morello.
是你啊  妹子
That's you, kid.
应该没人来看我啊  也许是我的妹妹
I'm not expecting anybody. Maybe it's my sister.
老天  希望没出事  我样子如何
Jeez, I hope there's nothing wrong. How do I look?
-漂亮  -好的
- Looking hot. - All right.
你够了
Stop!
至少进来让我可以看到你
Man, or at least get in here where I can see you.
你打算做这种无聊事做多久
How much longer is this shit gonna go on for?
你要拿去给红妈
You need to take it to Red.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你真觉得我会为了嗨一次
You really think I'm gonna throw
丢掉两年的戒毒成果吗
away two years of sobriety for one little high?
我看到崔希娅被装在运尸袋中被运出去
I saw Tricia get wheeled out of here in a body bag.
你觉得我有多蠢
How stupid do you think I am?
你好
Well, hello. Hi.
别碰我
Don't you fucking touch me.
坐下
Sit down.
很高兴见到你  我喜欢你的毛衣
It's nice to see you. I like your sweater.
听我说
Listen to me.
我知道你闯进了我家
I know you broke into my house.
我不知道你如何做到的  但你做到了
I don't know how you did it, but you did.
警察不相信我  但我知道是你
Now, the cops don't believe me, but I know it was you.
我不明白  你为什么来这里
I don't understand. Why did you come here?
因为我要听你承认
Because I want to hear you say it.
-告诉我是你  -我不知道你在说些什么
- Tell me it was you. - I don't know what you're talking about.
显然你坐牢这段时间
So, clearly your time in prison
并没有让你回归现实  你这个疯子
has done nothing to bring you back into reality, you psycho.
我对天发誓
I swear to God...
如果你再接近我  或是我的家人我的妻子
if you come near me, or my family, or my wife again, ever,
我会杀了你
I will kill you.
我会用双手  活活掐死你
With my bare fucking hands, I will choke you until you are dead.
你能小点声音吗
Could you keep your voice down just a little?
你有病吗  为什么
You... Are you out of... Why?
你让我小点声
You want me to keep my voice down
这样你的罪犯朋友不会知道
so your criminal friends in here won't know that you're a
你是个疯子  越狱跟踪我吗
mental case who broke out of prison to stalk me?
是他吗
Is that him?
什么意思
What is that?
你要继续玩这种疯子把戏吗
Are you trying to keep up this lunatic charade?
-假装我是你男友吗  -不是
- Pretend that I'm your boyfriend? - No.
我不认识这个女人  明白吗
I don't know this woman, okay?
我们约会过一次  就一次
We went on one date! One!
她是个该死的跟踪狂
She's a fucking stalker!
先生  请马上离开
Sir, you need to leave now.
她是个危险人物
She's fucking dangerous!
-马上离开  -她...
- Leave, now. - Hey... She...
你知道她越狱了吧
You know she broke out of here, right?
她是个疯婊子
She's a psycho bitch!
-对不起  -快走
- Sorry. - Come on.
我可不是有罪的那个
Hey, man, I'm not the criminal here, okay?
我疯了
I'm crazy.
我是个疯子  我真的很有问题
I'm a crazy person. There is something really wrong with me.
我们所有人都有问题
I mean, there's something wrong with all of us.
否则我们不会在这里
Like, otherwise we wouldn't be in here.
不  我做了坏事
No, I did something bad.
非常坏
Really bad.
我应该待在医院时
When I was supposed to be at the hospital,
我偷了车
I stole the van
去了他奥尔巴尼的家
and I went to his house in Albany.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
你知道如果你被抓的话会有什么后果吗
Do you know what could happen if you got caught?
我想他们会控告你重罪潜逃
I think they charge you with felony escape.
刑期延长三倍
Triple your sentence.
我知道  相信我  我知道
I know. Believe me, I know.
别他妈的再这样做了  你这个疯子
Well, don't fucking do that again, you maniac.
真的
Seriously.
你没被抓真是奇迹
It's a miracle that you didn't get caught.
我只是想见他
I just wanted to see him.
但他好恶毒  真的好恶毒
But he is so mean. I mean, he's really mean.
他不是我以为的那个人
He's not the man that I thought he was.
你恨我吗
Do you hate me?
不  我不恨你
No, I don't hate you.
但每一秒
Well, it is getting clearer
都越来越清楚你是个疯子
every second that you're totally bat-shit crazy,
但你是个美丽可人的女生
but you're a beautiful, sweet girl.
别去管这男人了  会有好多人爱你的
Fuck this guy. So many people are gonna love you.
不  没人会爱我
No. No, nobody's gonna love me.
我爱
I do.
过来
Come here.
莱瑞  是我
Hi, Larry. It's me.
我知道我说过
Listen, I know that I said
我不想知道是谁  我的确不想
I didn't wanna know who it was, and I didn't.
但在这里  就是会让人产生执念
But being in here, it just has a way of making you obsess
感觉有点疯狂
and feel a little crazy.
嫉妒
Jealous.
我知道这样不公平  但这是我的感觉
So, I know this is totally unfair, but it's how I feel.
所以我想如果我知道会好些
So I just think it would be better if I knew.
如果我知道是谁  我就不用再猜了
If I just knew who it was, and then I could stop guessing.
你的通话时间到了
Your phone time is up.
我刚刚...
I... I'm just...
再见
Um, bye.
这样就对了
That's right.
走人吧
Move along.
反正我也讲完了
I was done anyway.
我不是同性恋  我不是
I'm not gay. I'm not.
我只是在尝试
I'm just experimenting.
我不知道
I don't know.
也许一直以来我交往的男人
Maybe all of the guys that I've been with so far
在床上表现都很差
have just been really bad in bed,
但我告诉你
but I'm telling you,
就好像我刚发现性爱应该是什么样子
it's like I just discovered what sex is supposed to be.
-但她有女友  -是啊
- But she has a girlfriend? - Mmm...
她之前有女友
She had a girlfriend.
她们之间有问题  已经结束了
They were having problems. It's over.
-肯定吗  -是的
- For sure? - Yeah.
我不确定  帕波
I don't know, Piper.
是谁
Who is that?
我的天  我的天  袋里有屎
Oh, my God. Oh, my God! There's shit in that bag!
你居然被骗了  这可是最古老的恶作剧了
You fell for that? That's like the oldest trick in the book.
什么是最古老的恶作剧
What is the oldest trick in the book?
屎在袋子里  点起火吗
Poop? In a bag? On fire?
我哥和他的朋友以前经常这样做
Yes, my brother and his friends used to do it.
真他妈的蠢  纯粹恶作剧
It's so fucking stupid. It's a prank.
老天
Oh, my God.
-是她  -谁
- It's her. - Who?
-西尔维  艾丽克斯的前女友  -真的吗
- Sylvia. Alex's ex. - Really?
她是个疯婆子  她打了我
Yes, she's fucking crazy. She attacked me.
这是她做的  我知道
This is... This is her, I know it.
你觉得这是人屎吗
Do you think it's human shit?
不  这是狗屎  对吗
No, I mean, this is... This is dog shit, right?
如果她真的有你说的这样疯
I mean, if she's really as crazy as you say...
你不会觉得这是她蹲下拉在袋子里的吧
You don't think that she squatted and pooped in a bag, do you?
她的意思表达得很清楚了  佩服佩服
Well, she did get her point across. I'll give her that much.
女同都是疯子
Lesbians are insane.
我不敢相信她对你说这种话  好大的胆子
I can't believe she said that to you. The fucking nerve! Jesus.
她是对的
She was right.
我引诱了他  我们故意陷害他
I seduced him. We set him up.
但她不知道
Yeah, but she doesn't know that.
这样不对  他会坐牢  约翰
It's wrong. He's going to jail, John.
有其它办法吗  怎样  你想让我...
What is the alternative? What, you want me to...
你想让我站出来大声说
You want me to stand up and shout,
各位  她肚里是我的宝宝
"Hey, everyone, that's my baby in there"?
在我生活的地方
You know, in my neighborhood,
真男人会站出来承认自己的孩子
real men stand up and claim their kids.
我们不是在你生活的地方  不是吗
We're not in your neighborhood, are we?
你到底想要我怎样  达娅
I mean, what the fuck do you want from me, Daya?
我要你站出来告诉全世界你爱我
I want you to stand up and tell the world that you love me.
这太疯狂了
That is insane.
他们会把我推到媒体的峰尖浪口
They would cart me off in front of the local news.
-你想要这样吗  -不  是的
- Is that what you want? - No. Yes.
我不知道我想要什么  只是感觉很糟糕
I don't know what I want. It just feels really bad.
达娅  我会坐牢的
Daya, I would go to jail.
那样至少我们扯平了
Well, then at least we'll be even.
如果你是来嘲笑我的  我可没力气吵
If you're here to mock me, I don't have the energy to argue.
做什么都痛
Everything hurts.
我不是来取笑你的
I'm not here to make fun of you.
是吗
Really?
我昨天看到一位朋友被拉去关禁闭
I watched a friend get taken to the SHU yesterday.
那是她第二次被关禁闭
That's the second time she's been in there,
第一次很痛苦
and the first time was rough.
我已经厌恶厌倦了警卫把关禁闭
I'm sick and tired of the guards using solitary
当作是罚小孩子站墙角
like it's some kind of toddler timeout.
这些人不是暴力罪犯
These are not violent offenders.
这是不人道的  这是折磨
It's inhumane and it's torture.
我觉得你这样做  非常非常勇敢
I think what you're doing is very, very brave.
你是个真正的维权分子
You are a true activist.
你把我给你的传单发完了吗
Did you hand out all the flyers I gave you?
当然了  发了  长官
'Course I did. Yes, sir.
但我觉得没人会...
But I really don't think anybody's gonna...
我知道  德盖特  我明白
I know, Doggett. I got it.
-波丽  -你好
- Hey, Pol! - Hi.
老天  你好苗条
Oh, my gosh, you're so skinny.
你怀孕的肥屁股已经没有了
Your big pregnancy ass is gone!
我知道
I know.
抱歉好久没见了
I am so sorry it's been so long.
帕波  塞莱斯特的事我很遗憾
And, Pipe, I'm sorry about Celeste.
我应该去参加葬礼的  我只是
I should have been at the funeral. I just...
我的奶不多  挤奶太痛苦了
I'm not making that much milk, and pumping is really hard.
莱瑞说你现在是个二十四孝老妈
Larry says you've been lost in the baby fog.
我感觉好糟糕
I feel horrible.
你失去了亲人  我应该在你身边的
You lost someone. I should have been there for you.
真是对不起
I'm so, so sorry.
-我真是太差劲了  -别说了  没关系
- It was really shitty of me. - Stop, it's fine.
不  有关系
It's not. It's not fine.
你需要我我却不在  我是个差劲的朋友
You needed me and I wasn't there. I've been a really bad friend.
最差劲的朋友  你不应该有我这样的朋友
Like, the worst. You don't deserve that.
你不应该经历这些
You don't deserve any of this.
-当妈的感觉如何  -好难
- How is mommy life? - Hard.
比任何人讲的都难多了
It's so much harder than anyone tells you.
我觉得我失去理智了  我不再是自己了
I feel like I've lost my mind. I'm not myself.
-皮特还好吗  -皮特去了阿拉斯加
- Is Pete being good? - Pete took off to Alaska.
好奇怪  他太烦人了
It was weird and totally horrible of him.
你经常见莱瑞吗
Have you seen Larry a lot?
没有  为什么问  他说的吗
No. Why, did he tell you that?
只是皮特离开期间
I mean, just when Pete was gone.
芬恩的事他帮了我不少
He helped me a lot with Finn.
你们还经常通话吗
Are you guys still talking a lot?
我们刚在一起整整48小时
Well, we just spent the past 48 hours together.
怎么样
How did that go?
我们做爱了
We had sex.
我们开始了  在给我奶奶守灵时
Well, we started to. At my grandmother's wake.
是吗
Really?
你很惊讶吗
Does that surprise you?
是啊  我以为你和他结束了
Uh, well, yeah, I thought you ended things.
他曾经是我的未婚夫  波丽  还是有爱的
He was my fiance Polly. There's still a lot of love there.
当然
Of course.
他和别人上过床了
He slept with someone else.
是吗
Really?
他告诉你了吗
Did he tell you that?
没有  他为什么会告诉我
No, why would he tell me that?
你们一直有联系
You two... have been talking.
你们关系好  他帮你照顾芬恩
You're close. He's been helping you with Finn.
我们关系也没那么好
Oh, we're not that close.
他跟你怎么说的
Um... what did he tell you?
是我认识的人
That it was someone I know.
我想他感觉相当内疚
I think he was feeling pretty guilty.
他可能觉得那是一个错误
He probably felt like it was a mistake.
他不想伤害你
He doesn't want to hurt you.
我相信他不想
I'm sure that he doesn't.
你觉得她会谋杀我吗
Do you think she's gonna murder me?
这个西尔维到底有多不正常
Just how unstable is this Sylvia person?
-那是个玩笑  -那不是玩笑
- It was a joke. - It was not a joke!
那是个意思很清楚的口信
It was a very clear message.
我知道你做了什么  婊子
"I know what you did, bitch,
我要你知道我知道了
and I want you to know that I know."
和你在一起是我的选择
Look, being with you was my choice.
我之前不开心
I wasn't happy.
然后我利用了这点
And then I took advantage of that.
我是个成年人  帕波
I'm a grown-up, Piper.
你觉得她会来找我麻烦吗
Do you think that she's gonna come after me?
我觉得她需要的是
Look, I think that she needed to
发泄出来  明白吗
get it out of her system, all right?
有时候需要大怒一下才能放下
Sometimes you gotta rage in order to move on.
你爱过她吗
Did you love her?
没有
No.
但我爱你
But I love you.
真的吗
You do?
这话我可不是随便对每个人说的
I don't say that to everyone.
你得回应我
You have to say it back.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你想谈谈吗
Do you wanna talk about it?
不
No.
还记得我告诉你  我未婚夫干了别的女人吗
Remember I told you that my fiance fucked somebody else?
是的
Yeah.
是我最好的朋友
It was my best friend.
请让我一个人待下好吗
Can I be alone for a minute, please?
当然  亲爱的
Sure, honey.
亲爱的  自己喝下毒药是不可能杀死敌人的
Honey, you don't drink poison and wait for it to kill your enemy.
别再捶墙了  计划复仇吧
Stop hitting walls and plot your revenge.
妈的
Oh, fuck!
你他妈的在做什么
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
我想加入你的园艺俱乐部
You know, I think I'd like to join your little gardening club.
我们不接受新会员
We're not accepting new members.
挖隧道吗  红妈  你以为你是兔八哥啊
A tunnel, Red? That is so Bugs Bunny.
你打算怎么做  出卖我吗
What are you gonna do, turn me in?
不  我会用上这个
No, I'm gonna use it.
你有你自己的门路
You have your own operation.
我知道  但这个更好
Yeah, I know, but this is better.
更少的人参与  没有不稳定的供货联系
Fewer people involved and no unstable vendor connections.
-不可能归你  -不是的
- You're not taking it. - No, no, no, no, no.
我可不想夺走你的姑娘们的
I wouldn't want to deprive your girls
屎味的连裤袜
of their shit-flavored panty hose.
我们可以分享
We could share.
你不懂如何分享
You don't know how to share.
只会抢夺  只会欺凌弱小
Just to take and to bully.
我们曾经做过朋友
We used to be friends once.
我想再和你做朋友
I want to be friends again, man!
好个朋友
Some friend.
你会考虑下吗
Will you think about it, huh?
你也想想这些年你变了多少好吗
And would you think about how much you've changed over the years?
人会变  红妈
People change, Red.
妮琪
Nicky.
你觉得人会变吗
Do you think people can change?
好了
All right.
你把这个帮我拿走  因为我会吸
I need you to take this from me, 'cause I'm gonna do it.
但我真的真的不想
And I really, really don't want to.
谁给你的
Who gave that to you?
美味姐  维的货
Taystee. It came from Vee.
真是对不起  红妈  我让你失望了
I'm so sorry, Red. I let you down.
-你没有  -是嘛
- No, you didn't. - Yeah.
你拿来了
You brought it here.
你做得非常好  妮琪
You did good, Nicky.
你做到了
You did.
姑娘  稳着点
Hey, girl, steady there.
我很好  我没事
I'm fine. I'm good.
-维  -啥事
- Yo, Vee! - Yeah.
-操你妈  -妈的  妹子  你喝醉了
- Fuck you. - Oh, shit, girl, you blind drunk.
你要抢走我的工作
You want to take my fucking job assignment?
你要抢走我所有的朋友  操你妈
You want to take all my friends? Well, fuck you!
在她伤到自己之前  来个人把她弄走吧
Somebody get her out of here before she hurts herself.
操你妈
Fuck you!
妈的
Shit!
操你妈
Fuck you!
-妈的  -你别碰她
- Fuck! - Don't you touch her!
不不
No! No! No!
你不听话就会是这个下场
That's what you get when you don't listen!
就会是这个下场
That's what you get!
不
No.
喂
Hello?
利奇菲尔德联邦监狱的女犯打来电话
An inmate from Litchfield Federal Prison is attempting to contact you.
要接听电话  请按一
To accept this call, please press "One."
-卡尔的电话  -内莉  卡尔在吗
- Cal's phone. - Neri, hey, is Cal there?
他去树林觅食去了
No, he's out foraging in
去找吃起来有蔬菜味的蔬菜
the forest for greens that taste really green.
但他可能已经快好了  要我叫他吗
But he's probably almost done. Should I go get him?
也许你能帮我
Actually, maybe you can help me.
好啊  小姑子
Yeah, sister-in-law!
什么忙都行
Whatever you need, dude.
我需要你帮我一次
I need you to do me a favor.
一个大忙
It's a big one.
我活该
I deserve that.
-好啦  -嘿
- All right. - Hey.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
那就快滚
Then get the fuck out of here.
-什么事  -没什么
- What was that about? - Nothing.
你有没有见过一种画面  会烙在你的脑海里的
You ever seen an image that sears itself into your brain?
就像那部讲驴友的电影
Like the movie about the hiker guy,
他用瑞士军刀把自己的胳膊给切断了
where he cuts off his own arm with a Swiss Army knife?
那个声音  肌腱
Yeah, the sound, the tendons...
妈的
Fuck!
我真希望自己没看过那部分
I wish I never watched that part.
你知道什么让我觉得更恶心吗
You know what tops that for me?
什么画面让我忘不掉  在脑海里挥之不去
You know what image I can't unsee, it's still stuck in there,
一天至少想到一次  让我没胃口吃午饭
flickering at least once a day, making me want to lose my lunch?
不知道  先生
No, sir.
你的光屁股  门德斯
Your bare ass, Mendez.
你那长疙瘩的苍白屁股
Your pimply, white ass,
在扫把拖把间上上下下
bouncing up and down between the brooms and the mops,
撞击那可怜的姑娘
ramming into that poor girl.
一个你本应保护保障她安全的姑娘
A girl you were supposed to protect and keep safe.
你的屁股  像鬼一样缠着我
Your ass, it haunts me.
抱歉听到这个  先生
I'm sorry to hear that, sir.
我做这行已经25年了
I've been doing this kind of work 25 years.
就是像你这样的人  给了这份职业一个坏名声
And it's guys like you that give the whole profession a bad name.
如果我说了算
If it was up to me,
你永远别再想涉足这个地方
you'd never set foot on this property again.
但考虑到惩教署不提出起诉
But considering the DOC didn't press charges,
之前只是我们间的言语之争
it was your word against mine...
直到现在
until now.
我一直在本分工作  先生
Well, I've been doing my job, sir.
今天早上就记了15个过了
Just gave out 15 shots this morning.
你让她怀孕了
You got her pregnant.
不
No.
对她来说很不幸  是的
Sadly for her, yes.
那个可怜的姑娘怀上了
That poor girl is carrying around
一个大胡子虐待狂的孽种
a sadistic little mustachioed shit inside her.
-哇  -门德斯
- Whoa. - Mendez...
你他妈的被炒了
you're fucking fired.
我明白  先生
I understand, sir.
不  我想你没明白
No, I... I don't think you do understand.
你还被逮捕了
You're also under arrest.
我们到了
We're in.
我来吧
Let me get that for ya.
好了  咱们走
All right, let's go.
我们在利奇菲尔德联邦监狱现场报导
We're reporting from Litchfield Federal Penitentiary,
狱警乔治・门德斯被逮捕
where the arrest of Correctional Officer George Mendez
他被起诉性侵犯  逮捕正在进行中
on charges of sexual assault is underway.
她来了
There she is!
我旁边是娜塔莉・菲格罗亚
I'm here with Natalie Figueroa,
利奇菲尔德联邦监狱的助理典狱长
Assistant Warden of Litchfield prison,
她是杰森・菲格罗亚的妻子
and wife of Jason Figueroa,
后者现正竞选州参议员
who is currently running for state senate.
菲格罗亚夫人
Miss Figueroa,
你知道警员中有不当行为存在吗
were you aware of misconduct among your officers?
在利奇菲尔德
Here at Litchfield,
我们对性罪犯者
we have a zero-tolerance
是绝对不会容忍的
policy when it comes to sexual offenders.
自《消除监狱强奸法案》颁布以来
Since the Prison Rape Elimination Act,
消除恶劣警员便成了我们的任务
we have made it our mandate to weed out rogue officers.
这些无助的女性在我们的照顾下
These vulnerable women are under our care,
我们会尽一切能力去保护她们
and we do everything in our power to protect them.
当然  这个世界上依然有坏人
Of course, there are still bad people in this world
会犯下十恶不赦的罪行
who commit heinous crimes,
不幸的是
and it is unfortunate that
其中一个道德败坏的人  居然在我们这里
one of these sickos ended up under our roof.
但我向你保证  我们会尽一切力量
But I assure you, we are doing everything in our power
照顾这位年轻女性
to take care of this young woman,
她才是真正的受害者
who is the real victim here.
-等我  亲爱的  -快走
- Wait for me, baby. - All right, keep it moving.
知道吗  我不在乎了
You know what? I don't care anymore.
来吧  逮捕我
Go ahead, arrest me!
我爱这个女人
I love this woman!
你听到我的话吗
You hear me?
她怀的是我的宝宝  老子爱死你了
That is my baby in there, and I fucking love you!
我要给孩子取名叫斯坦  好吗
I want to call it Stan, okay?
别举重东西
Don't lift anything heavy!
别吃吞拿鱼  也别吃软芝士
And no tuna fish! Or soft cheese.
我会回来找你的  亲爱的
I'm coming back for you, baby!
我会照顾你的  照顾你们母子
I'm gonna take care of you! Both of you!
快走  这里没你事了
Let's go. You're done here.